http://www.nsra.co.uk/index.php/home/reference/codes-guidance/nsra-privacy-policy

Feedback
You are here:
NSRA Privacy Policy
The NSRA has updated its Privacy Policy to better present how we collect, store and process Personal Information. It can be downloaded via the link below:
Privacy Policy
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any update on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 20th May 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
By e-mail: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.By mail: NSRA, Lord Roberts Centre, Bisley Camp, Brookwood, Surrey GU24 0NP
In This Section
Reference
Reference Section
Organisation
Rules
Codes and Guidance
Introduction
Constitutions
Diary Dates
The calendar will be republished as soon as we are able to confirm which events are going ahead this year and in 2021.
National Small-bore Rifle Association, Lord Roberts Centre, Bisley Camp,Woking, Surrey. GU24 0NPTel. 01483 485502/485503Fax. 01483 476392
Search...
To Top
We use cookies on our website. Some of them are essential for the operation of the site, while others help us to improve this site and the user experience. We do not use any cookies to collect or share personal information. You can decide for yourself whether you want to allow cookies or not. Please note that if you reject them, you may not be able to use all the functionalities of the site.
Ok Decline
More information
